简直没个完
Okay, that was interminable.
15个PPT展示
How are 15 PowerPoint presentations
怎么就"独特的调研机会了"
a "unique research opportunity"?
你们还说犯罪现况报告很"有趣"呢
You guys said crime-stat briefings were "fascinating."
等等  你们是这么跟他说的
Wait a minute. You guys told him that?
肯定会有人觉得有趣吧
Well, I'm... I'm sure they're fascinating to someone.
天呐  你们骗我
Oh, my... you lied to me.
我刚刚浪费了我人生的三个小时啊
I just squandered three hours of my life.
我们不也是
So did we.
得了  卡塞尔  别生气嘛
Oh, come on, Castle. No hard feelings.
这样吧  我们老地方
I'll tell you what... I will buy the first round
-我买第一轮酒  -抱歉了
- at the old haunt. - Sorry, guys.
今晚不行
I can't tonight.
我要跟姐夫去做保镖
I have another security gig with my brother-in-law.
不是吧  又来
Really? Again?
对  好消息是
Yeah, the good news is
萨拉·格蕾丝这下有钱上大学了
Sarah Grace will have enough money for college.
不过等我累死  她就没机会见到我了
The bad news is she'll have no idea who I am.
这次保卫谁
So, who are you guarding this time?
事实上  我不能说
The truth is, I'm not allowed to say.
什么意思嘛
What you mean, you're not allowed to say?
是我们啊  是谁啊
It's us. Who is it?
真的  我不能说啊
Seriously, man. I can't.
那么都不是一般的职业运动员或真人秀明星了
That means this goes beyond the usual pro athlete or reality star.
是个重要人物啊  有地位的人物
This is someone important, someone revered.
教皇吗
Perhaps the pope?
达赖喇嘛  安吉拉·默克尔
The Dalai Lama? Angela Merkel?
我不会说的
My lips are sealed.
莱恩  是单向乐队吗
Ryan! Is it One Direction?!
如果是他们  你会告诉我吧  他们来了吗
You'd tell me, right? Are they in town?
-他们在香港  -好吧
- No, they're in Hong Kong. - Right.
我姐姐怎么样了
Hey, how's my sister doing?
现在我不当警察了  她睡得更安生了
Sleeping easier now that I retired from the force.
你一点不怀念风化组的工作吗
You don't miss the job at all, working vice?
不
Nah.
那时候我成天跟下层人渣打交道
I was dealing with lowlifes every waking minute.
现在我自己能做主了  真的  凯文
Now I'm my own boss. I'm telling you, Kev.
做保镖是更好的选择
Security is a better way of life.
我得说  很多退休的警察
I have to say, a... a lot of guys when they retire,
都找不到方向了
they just drift,
但你干得真不错
but you're really making this work.
你也可以这样
You could make it work for you, too.
总之  只要你决定
Well... anyhow, there's a permanent spot for you
我就能给你个铁饭碗
with me the minute you make the call.
弗兰克
Wow, Frank.
这太慷慨了
That's a hell of an offer.
凭你的背景  有你是我走运了
Well, with your background, I'd be lucky to have you.
告诉我  滋事人员都记住了吧
Now tell me, did you memorize the rogue's gallery?
当然  每张脸都背住了
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Every face.
-危险程度有多高  -很低的
- So, what's the threat level here? - Low.
是干净水源的慈善活动
It's a charity event for pure water now.
又不是中东和平大会
It's not a middle east peace conference.
肯定会有抗议者去打扰洛佩兹议员
There's gonna be protesters who want to bother congressman Lopez.
-你听说过他吧  -当然  谁没有啊
- You've heard of him, right? - Yeah, yeah. Who hasn't?
在议院顺风顺水
He's a rising member of the house,
很有号召力  但说实话
super-charismatic, but let's face it,
议院里也拔不出几个像样的
there's not a hell of a lot of competition in that.
他这人还是很不错的
He's still a stand-up guy.
他每次进城都雇我
Every time he comes to the city, he hires me,
-把他照顾好了  -好的
- so treat him right. - All right.
他这人有前途的
He's going places.
-什么时候到  弗兰克  -就几分钟了
- What's our E.T.A., Frank? - Just a few more minutes, sir.
凯文·莱恩警探  亚历克斯·洛佩兹议员
Detective Kevin Ryan, congressman Alex Lopez.
弗兰克对你评价很高呢
Frank speaks very highly of you.
-他对您也是  先生  -得了
- As he does of you, sir. - Oh, please.
叫我亚历克斯就行  洛佩兹先生也可以  随你
Call me Alex. Or Mr. Lopez, if you want.
这是我妻子  米娅
My wife, Mia.
你见过了我的幕僚长  梅根·布鲁克斯
You've met my chief of staff, Megan Brooks.
凯文  你觉得你今晚的职责是什么
Kevin, what do you think your job is tonight?
保护您  先生
To protect you, sir.
其实你更多是要保护我的名誉
Mostly it's my reputation you need to protect.
如今  一张照片就能毁了我
These days, a single photo can cause major damage
如果有哪个白痴凑过来想闹事的话
if some idiot approaches, tries to create a scene.
我们一定会确保不会发生这种事  先生
We'll make sure that doesn't happen, sir.
很好  等到了竞选季
Good, because come campaign season,
我可能会需要一些能依靠的人
I may need some men I can rely on.
先生  关于今晚的安排
Sir, about tonight's schedule.
先是走红毯  然后喝酒交际
It's the red carpet and then mingling over cocktails.
这些是您得结交的人
Uh, these are the people that you're gonna want to connect with.
有些您已经认识
Some of them you know.
都是有超级政治行动委员会的重要捐助人
All of them are major donors with their own super PACs,
而且目前还未背书任何候选人
who are still looking for a candidate that they can believe in.
我分析了他们过去的竞选捐助
I've broken down all of their past campaign contributions
-和净值  -希望这些有钱人
- and net worth. - I hope all these rich guys
都愿意拿出点他们的钱
are ready to fork over some of their money
给卡洛琳和她的干净水源项目
to Carolyn and her pure water project.
他们会的  亲爱的
Oh, they are, darling.
但他们真实的目的是来见你
But the real reason they're coming is to see you.
招呼打完之后
Okay, after meet-and-greets,
您要上台介绍卡洛琳
you're gonna take the stage and introduce Carolyn,
这是您的讲稿
and here is your speech.
打扰  各位  我们要停车了
Excuse me, folks. We're pulling in now.
议员先生  筹款进行得如何了
Congressman, how's your fundraising?
女士  您会支持您丈夫吗
Miss, are you going to stand by your husband?
多谢前来
Thank you so much for coming.
洛佩兹议员  您即将启动
Congressman Lopez, any truth to the rumor
总统竞选的传言是否属实
that you're launching a presidential campaign?
布瑞  今晚的重点
Now, Bree, tonight is all about
是我的好友卡洛琳·戴克
my very good friend Carolyn Decker
和她的干净水源项目
and her pure water project.
她将为全球的家庭
She's gonna be providing clean water
提供干净的用水
for families all over the globe.
这项工作多亏了亚历克斯·洛佩兹这样的人
Work that is only possible because of the support
支持和慷慨相助才得以开展
and generosity of people like Alex Lopez.
这是什么  血吗  你要拿这个喷在他身上吗
What is this, blood? What, were you gonna spray him with it?
他支持的无人机打击杀害无辜儿童
The drone strikes that he supports kill innocent children.
关押他  把他带走
Detain him and get him out of here.
干得好
Nice work.
你现在保护的这个人
You might find yourself protecting
可能将会成为第一位拉丁裔美国总统
the first Latino President of the United States.
在这呢
There he is.
恭喜你  吉姆
Congratulations, Jim.
州党主席  太适合你了
State party chairman, it's a great fit for you.
谢谢你一直以来的支持  亚历克斯
Well, thank you for all your support, Alex.
等你竞选总统时
You know I'll have your back
我也会支持你的
when you make a run for that White House.
八字还没一撇呢
A little too soon for that kind of talk,
-不过很感谢你这么说  -玩得愉快
- But I appreciate the thought. - Enjoy your evening.
-你也是  -好的
- Likewise. - All right.
谢尔顿先生  很高兴见到你
Mr. Shelton, it's a pleasure to see you.
你对自己的抱负很含蓄啊  亚历克斯
You're being very coy about your aspirations, Alex.
很显然你有很大的抱负
But you obviously have some,
-否则你也不会来这了  -目前来说
- or you wouldn't be here. - Well, for now,
我能为自己选区的人民服务就很高兴了
I'm just happy to serve the people of my district.
我说话很直接
Being coy isn't in my nature.
你还有你的想法并不是这个国家所需要的
You and your ideas aren't what this country needs,
我一定不会让你当上总统的
and I'll see to it that you never become President.
先生
Sir.
很高兴跟你谈话
Nice talking to you.
安亚娜·琼斯  这位是亚历克斯·洛佩兹
Aryana Jones, this is Alex Lopez.
安亚娜  我妻子和我都非常喜欢你
Aryana, my wife and I are huge fans.
等不及要看你今晚的演出了
Can't wait to see the performance tonight.
你人真好  亚历克斯
You are too sweet, Alex.
演出结束后一定要来跟我们见见
Please come say hi after the show.
先生
Sir.
还有五分钟就要开始了
Five minutes until you're on.
最好去后台准备一下
You better get backstage.
好的  好的  再见
Okay. Okay. Bye.
各位  我想跟卡洛琳单独谈谈
Give me some room, fellas. I'd like a word with Carolyn.
天啊  洛佩兹太受欢迎了
Man, Lopez is a rock star.
是啊  可不是嘛
Yeah, you're telling me.
好了  我会在台上保护他
All right, I'll keep eyes on him onstage.
-这就交给你了  -好的  明白
- You cover him back here? - Yeah, copy that.
天呐  我好像中枪了
Oh, God, I think I've been hit.
先生  不要动  医生马上就来了  好吧
Sir, stay right where you are. Help's on the way, okay?
卡洛琳
Carolyn...
卡洛琳  你不会有事的
Carolyn, you're gonna be all right.
凯文
Kev!
凯文  发生了什么
Kev, what the hell happened?
快报警  现在需要医生
Call 911. We need a doctor in here right now.
天啊  谁干的  你看见是谁了吗
God. Who did this? Did you see who did this?
没有  没有  没有
No. No, no, no, no.
站住  穿灰西服那个  别跑
Stop! Gray suit! Stay right where you are!
纽约警察  拦着那个人
NYPD! Stop that man!
警察  让开  快让开
Police! Clear out of the way! Move out of the away!
不许动  放下武器  别动
Freeze! Drop the weapon! Stay where you are!
把武器放下  把武器放下
Drop the weapon! Put the weapon down!
枪手要跑了
The shooter's getting away!
马上把枪放下  否则我要开枪了
Put the gun down now, or I'll shoot!
洛佩兹怎么样了
Hey, how's Lopez?
很幸运
Lucky.
子弹打中了他的锁骨  不过没打到心脏
The round hit his collarbone, but missed his heart.
卡洛琳·戴克怎么样了
How about Carolyn Decker?
还在做手术
Still in surgery.
我的视线就离开了一秒钟
I took my eyes off him for one second.
不不不  凯文  我们会找到枪手的
No, no, no, kev. We are gonna find this shooter.
纽约警察把周围十个街区都封锁了
NYPD sealed off 10 square blocks from this place.
-有人知道枪手的样子吗  -只有你描述的
- Did we get a description? - Only the one you gave us...
一米八多  中等身材  褐色头发
six feet, medium build, brown hair.
不是吗  没人看见他的脸吗
Come on. No one saw his face?
看见了  不过都太惊慌了  没记住
Yeah, they did, but they were too busy panicking to remember.
你来回忆一下刚才的事好吗
Look, why don't we walk through what happened?
不用了  弗兰克  我已经回忆过了
No, Frank. I already did that.
再回忆一遍又没害处
And what's the harm in doing it again?
好吧
Yeah.
Okay.
枪响了  有三声
Shots rang out, three of 'em.
我扑向洛佩兹  也把卡洛琳带倒了
I-I-I dove onto Lopez, took Carolyn down, too.
我看见他们受伤了  这时你来了
I saw they were hit. That's when you came in.
然后我发现了枪手  不过只看到他的背影
And then I spotted the shooter. And I only ever saw the back.
好吧  想想他的手
All right, think about his hands.
有没有戴戒指  手表什么的
Rings on his fingers, a watch?
没有  没有  什么都没戴
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah. Nothing like that.
等等
Wait.
蓝色卡片
Blue card.
是的  他脖子上挂着一张淡蓝色的身份卡
Yeah, he had a pale-blue I.D. card hanging from his neck.
他有媒体通行证
This guy had a press pass.
-凯文  太好了  -嗯
- Kev, that's good. - Yeah.
-我去告诉纽约警察  -好的
- I'm gonna brief the NYPD. - Okay.
坏事传千里
Bad news travels fast.
-你还好吗  -不太好
- Are you okay? - No, not really.
能以后再说吗
Can we talk later?
不行  凯文  这事不能等
No. Kev, this can't wait.
贝克特  我要查这个案子
Beckett, I have to work this case.
听我说  现在是凶杀案了
Look, it's a homicide now.
我在医院
I'm at the hospital.
卡洛琳·戴克刚才在手术中身亡了
Carolyn Decker just died in surgery.
凯文  你还在听吗
Kev? Are you there?
是的  我在
Yeah, I'm here.
我看了你的口供  我们应该谈谈
I read your statement. We should talk about it.
不不  没用  我没看到枪手的脸
No, no. There's no point. I never saw the shooter's face.
不过
But...
你跟洛佩兹谈过吗
have you talked to Lopez yet?
-没有  怎么了  -凶手在他的视线范围内
- No, why? - The shooter was in his line of sight.
-如果有人看见过他  一定是洛佩兹  -好的
- If anyone saw him, it was Lopez. - Okay.
我去查  一有结果我就通知你
I'm on it. I'll call you as soon as I know something.
抱歉  先生  这个地方闲人免进
I'm sorry, sir. This area's off-limits.
卡洛琳是我女儿
Carolyn is my daughter.
我很遗憾  先生
I'm very sorry, sir.
她只是想要帮助别人
All she ever tried to do was help people.
为什么是她
Why her?
凯文
Kev.
在  媒体通行证查得怎么样
Yeah. A-any luck on that press pass?
-那张卡是谁的  -谁的也不是
- Who did it belong to? - No one.
什么叫"谁的也不是"
What do you mean, "No one"?
保安有多余的通行证
Event security kept extra passes on hold
留给那些临时出现的人
for last-minute attendees.
枪手不知道从哪弄到了一张
So somehow our shooter got ahold of one.
-该死的  -是啊
- Damn it. - Yeah.
莱恩怎么样了
So, how's Ryan doing?
他明白那不是他的错  对吧
He knows it's not his fault, right?
毕竟是在他眼皮底下发生的
Well, it happened on his watch.
对他来说  在找到凶手之前
So for Ryan, it means it's all on him
一切都要算在他头上
until he finds this guy.
贝克特探长  我是吉姆·博伊斯  州党主席
Detective Beckett, Jim Boyce, state party chair.
这整件事真是太可怕了
This whole thing is just terrible.
有什么消息吗
Is...there any news?
我们正在竭尽全力逮捕嫌疑人
Just that we're doing everything we can to apprehend the suspect.
我很高兴是你接手了这案子
Well, I'm glad that you're the one handling the case.
抱歉  博伊斯先生  我们认识吗
I'm sorry, Mr. Boyce. Do we know each other?
不  但你盛名在外
No, but you have an outstanding reputation,
连我身边的人都知道
and it's gotten the attention of the people in my world.
我就不耽误你了  探长
I won't hold you, detective.
-幸会  -彼此彼此
- Pleasure to meet you. - Yeah, likewise.
什么情况
What was that about?
不知道
I have no idea.
也许我们能以卡洛琳的名义建立一个基金
Maybe we can set up a foundation in Carolyn's name.
好的  奖学金之类的
Yes, let's do that. Like a-a scholarship fund.
不如我去查查  然后给你们意见吧
Why don't I look into that and get back to you with options.
那真是再好不过了  布鲁克斯
That would be great, Megan.
洛佩兹议员  我是贝克特探长
Congressman Lopez, I'm detective Beckett.
这位是卡塞尔先生
This is Mr. Castle.
我们在调查枪击案
We're investigating the shooting.
作为一名政客
You know, as a politician...
你一早就知道可能会受到伤害
...you know in the back of your mind that harm may come to you,
但绝不该殃及到无辜的人
But it should never come to an innocent bystander.
议员先生  案发之前您有留意到
Congssman, did you notice anything
任何可疑的人或事吗
or anyone suspicious prior to the shooting?
一切都很正常
Everything seemed normal.
-直到出事  -我们确信枪击
- Until it wasn't. - Well, we believe that the shots originated
来自舞台的最北边
from the north end of the backstage area.
也就是你跟卡洛琳·戴克交谈时
That's the direction you were facing
你正对着的方向
when you were speaking with Carolyn Decker.
你有注意到后面有任何可疑的人吗
Did you notice anyone in the background?
我看到了
I saw...
舞台工作人员  制作团队...
stagehands, production crew...
有一个人
There was this one guy.
他穿的什么
What was he wearing?
灰色西装
A gray suit.
是他吗
Is that him?
就是他杀了卡洛琳吗
Is that the man that killed Carolyn?
你有看到他的样貌吗  能形容一下吗
Did you see his face? Can you describe him?
我记得一清二楚
I can most definitely describe him.
这就是我们要找的人  艾里克·钱伯斯
This is our guy, Eric Chambers...
边缘博客写手  极端的政治活动者
Fringe blogger and political activist with some pretty extreme ideas.
他跟画像的确很相像
Okay, he looks like the sketch,
但他有出现在犯罪现场吗
But can we place him at the crime scene?
鉴证组在墙上发现了他的指纹  他当时在场
CSU pulled chambers' print off the wall, so he was there.
绝对是他
It's definitely him.
我猜他不太支持洛佩兹吧
I'm guessing he's not a big supporter of Lopez?
这么形容可太轻了
That's an understatement.
两周前  他在博客上痛骂了洛佩兹
Two weeks ago, chambers ranted on his blog
说他威胁到了美国人的生活方式
about how Lopez posed a threat to the American way of life
还说他将得到叛国者应得的报应
and that he would get what all traitors deserve.
-钱伯斯现在在哪  -他最近的地址在包厘街
- Where is Chambers now? His last known address was in the bowery.
-战术组已经去了  -带上莱恩
- Tactical's gearing up. - Take Ryan.
你们逮捕钱伯斯时应该让他在场
He should be there when you pick Chambers up.
战术组还有三分钟就到
Tactical's about three minutes out.
我们怎么确定钱伯斯在家
How do we know Chambers is at home?
托瑞锁定了他的手机  他就在里面
Tory pinged his cell. He's in there.
哥们儿  我们会抓住他的
Hey, bro. We're gonna get this guy.
就是他
There he is.
他要跑
He's on the move!
钱伯斯  不许动
Chambers, freeze!
钱伯斯
Chambers!
放开我
Get the hell off me!
你们不能这样
You can't do this!
给我个理由杀你啊
Give me a reason!
艾里克·钱伯斯  你被捕了
Eric Chambers, you're under arrest.
我们抓到他了  莱恩  没事了
We got him, Ryan. We're good.
钱伯斯先生  你将面临谋杀
Mr. Chambers, you are facing charges for murder
和企图刺杀国会议员未遂的指控
and the attempted assassination of a congressman.
争取宽大的最好办法就是坦白认罪
Your best hope for leniency is to confess.
我不会认罪的  我不会满足你们的
I'll never confess. I won't give you the satisfaction.
那你不如将这当做一次机会
Okay, why don't you consider this a chance
从你的角度说说怎么回事吧
to tell your side of the story?
我的角度就是我是无辜的
My side of the story is that I'm innocent.
这一切都是假的
This is all a charade.
证据显示可不是如此
The evidence would suggest otherwise.
我们在你的公寓发现了这张被偷的记者证
We found this stolen press pass at your apartment
还有一张舞厅的平面图
along with a floor plan of the ballroom.
并且你在枪击发生后就逃离了现场
Then there's the pesky issue of you fleeing after firing the shots.
一个真正的爱国者  从定义上就是国家的敌人
A true patriot, by definition, is an enemy of the state.
我们的政府在起诉我这样的人方面
Our government has a long and sorry history
可有着悠久而不堪的历史
of persecuting people like me.
这么说  你还成被害人了
So, you are the victim here?
而你们就是他们用来摧毁我的工具
And you're the instrument they're using to try to destroy me.
你们太盲目了  看不到这其实是个剧本
You're too blind to see that this is a script.
你们只是在扮演其中的角色
You're just playing your part.
这就是最让我不解的地方了
Um, okay, here's the part that fascinate me.
你恨洛佩兹  你希望他死
You hated Lopez. You wanted him dead.
所以你开枪打了他
So you shot him.
虽然并没致命
Not fatally, it turns out.
但你仍为各地的"真正的爱国者"发出了一击
But still, you struck a blow for "True patriots" everywhere.
这不正是你此生最荣耀的时刻吗  艾里克
Isn't this the proudest moment of your life, Eric?
为什么不承认呢
I mean, why not own it?
为什么不承认你的壮举呢
Why not take credit for what you've accomplished?
你希望上庭  这样就会有人开论坛纪念你了
You want your day in court so you can have a public forum.
我没什么好说的了
I'm done here.
钱伯斯不肯开口
Chambers isn't talking.
可能不重要了
Well, that may not matter.
我们应该发现犯罪用枪了
I think we literally just found the smoking gun.
听好  警员在
Get this...UNIs found
离酒店大约一个街区距离的雨水沟里
a.38-caliber pistol in a storm drain
发现了一把0.38口径的手枪  最近才开过
about a block away from the hotel, recently fired.
-活动场地不是有金属探测器吗  -对
- Weren't there metal detectors at the venue? - Yeah.
也就是说枪可能是早就藏在酒店里
Which means that the gun might have been waiting for him,
-等着他去取的  -还有记者证
- stashed at the hotel. - Along with the press pass.
也就是说  他不是独自作案的
So, that suggests he wasn't acting alone.
洛佩兹可能仍是他同伙的目标
And Lopez might still be a target.
我去打给医院加强警戒
I'll call down to the hospital and beef up security.
如果弄清钱伯斯在案发现场的行动
If we can reconstruct Chambers' movements from the venue,
也许就能知道他是如何弄到的枪
we might be able to figure out how he got that gun.
还能找到他的共犯
And who he was working with.
在我们试图确认钱伯斯的身份时
You know, when we were trying to I.D. Chambers,
我们收集了活动的数百张照片
we rounded up hundreds of photos from that event.
我想我知道怎么找
I think I know where to start.
有些是摄影师拍的
Some were taken by photographers,
其他是客人用手机拍的
others by guests on their cellphones.
我用了面部扫描系统试着搜索钱伯斯
I used facial recognition to try and search for Chambers.
找到他了吗
Did you find him?
14张照片中有他  大多都在背景中
He appears in 14 pictures, mostly in the background.
因为每张照片都有时间戳
Since each photo is time-stamped,
所以可以构架出他在现场的行动
I was able to plot his movement at the venue.
每个点就代表钱伯斯被拍到的位置
Each dot represents where Chambers was photographed.
照片中有人曾交给过他东西吗
Does anyone in the photos ever hand him something?
他有拿到过手枪大小的东西吗
Does he ever retrieve an object the size of a gun?
恐怕没有  但有五分钟钱伯斯的
I'm afraid not, but there is a five-minute gap
行动是未知的
when chambers is unaccounted for.
这是缺失时段前的最后一张照片
This is the last photo before the missing time.
那个门通向一个储藏间
That door leads to a storage area.
-也许枪就藏在里面  -不不不
- Then maybe that's where the gun was stashed. - No. No, no.
按照安全规程  晚宴时那扇门
Security protocol would have had that door locked
-该是锁上的  -但这间没有锁
- for the evening. - Well, this room wasn't locked.
这个时段左右还有一张照片拍到了这里
Here's another picture of it taken around the same time.
那个人是酒店的工作人员
That guy works for the hotel.
如果那扇门应该是锁着的
If that door was supposed to be locked,
那他进去是要做什么
what was he doing in there?
朱利安·贝利
Julian Bailey?
有事吗
Yes?
你介意告诉我们
Do you mind telling us
昨晚你进储藏间做什么去了吗
what you were doing in the storage room last night?
我没进什么储藏间
I wasn't in any storage room.
那么这是谁  你的邪恶双胞胎吗
Oh, then who's this? Your evil twin?
好吧
Okay, yeah.
我溜进去见了个女孩
I snuck in there for a girl, you know?
我们约在那里见  但她却没来
We were gonna meet up, but she never showed.
好吧  你见过这个人吗
All right. Have you seen this guy?
他倒是进来了
Yeah, he came in the room.
我是不该进那间屋子的
I wasn't supposed to be there,
-所以我就藏起来了  -他进去干了什么
- so I hid. - What was he doing in the room?
在找东西吗  他是不是拿了把枪
Was he looking for something? Did he have a gun?
枪  不是  他和另一个人在一起
A gun? No, he was with another dude.
他们在很紧张的交谈
They were talking all intense.
关于何时何地
We have to be smart
干掉洛佩兹我们必须要谨慎
about when and where we bring Mr. Lopez down.
我都计划好了  好吗
I've got it covered, okay?
洛佩兹会得到报应的
Lopez is gonna get what's coming to him.
你之前怎么不说这事
And you didn't think to mention this before?
我害怕被解雇
I was afraid I'd get fired.
再说  等我意识到
Plus, by the time I realized he was the one
他就是枪击了议员的人时  你们都抓到他了
who shot the congressman, you guys had already caught him.
好吧  和他交谈的另一个人
All right, this other dude that he was talking to,
你看到他的脸了吗
did you see his face?
他们出门的一瞬间看到了一下
Just for a second as the two of them were walking out.
卡尔·谢尔顿
Carl Shelton?
那个亿万富翁兼实业家卡尔·谢尔顿
As in billionaire industrialist Carl Shelton?
是的  而且他很讨厌洛佩兹
Yeah, and he's no fan of Lopez.
我看到了谢尔顿当面告诉洛佩兹
I saw Shelton tell Lopez to his face
他绝对当不上总统
that he would never become president.
也许谢尔顿是想确保这点
Maybe Shelton wanted to make sure,
所以就串通了钱伯斯
so he colluded with Chambers.
很有可能
It's starting to look that way,
尤其是谢尔顿还是酒店的共有人
especially since Shelton is co-owner of this hotel.
也就是说他能弄到一张记者证
Which means he would have access to a press pass
而且也知道怎么带枪过安检
and know how to get a gun past security.
金钱与权利的对抗  企业大亨与政治家之战
It's money versus power, tycoon versus politician --
从美国建国就开始有这种事了
a story as old as America itself.
那我们就试着查查艾里克·钱伯斯
All right, let's try and find out what the connection is
和卡尔·谢尔顿的联系吧
between Eric Chambers and Carl Shelton.
我想谢尔顿先生恐怕不认识
I'm afraid Mr. Shelton does not know anyone
-什么艾里克·钱伯斯  -我们有目击者
- named eric chambers. - Well, we have a witness
看到你们两人在交谈
that saw the two of you talking to each other.
是目击者看错了
That witness is mistaken.
谢尔顿先生
Mr. Shelton,
你在资助一个叫做美国至上的组织
you financed a group called America for Americans.
它的创始人之一就是艾里克·钱伯斯
It's co-founded by Eric Chambers.
-我的委托人  -我
- My client -- - I...
我资助了很多草根组织
I fund many grassroots organizations
但凡和我一样关心这个
who share my concern about the decline
伟大国家前程的组织我都资助  但我并不
of this great nation, but I'm not acquainted
认识每个组织的每个人
with every person in every group.
艾里克·钱伯斯恐怕很难忽视吧
Eric Chambers' views are hard to miss.
他倡议居民武装起来
He advocates armed resistance
反抗他所谓的美国极权主义
against what he calls "The U.S. police state."
我认为美国公民武装起来
Well, there's nothing wrong with ordinary Americans
反抗政府的过度管控没什么错
defending themselves against government overreach.
但这事并非过度管控
Well, this isn't about overreach,
而是你个人想要消灭一个
This is about you getting rid of a politician
意见不合的政敌
who stood against you.
你在说什么  卡塞尔先生
W-what is that, Mr. Castle?
你新写的小说吗
Your latest work of fiction?
我想面谈该结束了吧
I believe that concludes our interview.
如果你还有问题  请带传票来
If you have more questions, get a subpoena.
谢尔顿先生  这事是你指使钱伯斯干的
Mr. Shelton, you put Chambers up to this
而我会证明这点
and I intend to prove it.
祝你好运了
Good luck with that.
怎么了  哥们儿
What's up, bro?
大家都走了  你怎么还在这儿
Everyone's gone. What you still doing here?
思考
Thinking.
好啦  我们破案了  凶手都抓住了
Come on. This is a win. We got the shooter.
谢尔顿呢
What about Shelton?
我们会起诉他的
We'll build a case against him.
我打赌钱伯斯会帮忙  供出谢尔顿的
And I bet that Chambers will help us out and roll on Shelton.
那他为什么还没供出他呢
Why hasn't he done that already?
也许谢尔顿许诺了钱伯斯
Maybe Shelton made Chambers some promises
某种好处作为封口费
in return for him keeping his mouth shut.
谢尔顿这样地位的人为什么要冒险
Why would a man in Shelton's situation
被人看见和钱伯斯在一起呢
risk being seen with Chambers?
因为他和其他那些富有的混蛋一样
Because he's like all these other rich sons of bitches
以为钱能摆平一切麻烦
who think they can get away with anything.
我不知道  这事有点不对劲  哈维
I don't know. Something about this just isn't sitting right, Javi.
你现在思维不清楚
You're spinning.
你只需要好好睡上一晚
You just need a good night's sleep.
明早一切就都清楚了
In the morning, everything will be clear to you.
好吗
All right?
喂
Hello.
什么
What?!
好的  现在怎么样
Right. How about now?
-看起来不错  -好
- That looks good. - Okay.
太好了  你来了
Oh! Good, you're here.
这是什么  你们在干什么
What is this? What are you guys doing?
莱恩在这忙了一整晚  他发短信叫我来
Ah, well, Ryan was working all night, and he texted me.
你叫卡塞尔却不叫我
You texted Castle and not me?
想出疯狂的推理时
Well, when you have a crazy theory,
你是不会叫理智的人来的
you don't call the voice of reason.
什么  什么推理
What -- what theory?
艾里克·钱伯斯不是开枪的人
Eric Chambers is not our shooter.
我们抓错人了
We got the wrong guy.
你说艾里克·钱伯斯不是开枪的人吗
You're telling me Eric Chambers is not our shooter?
有什么根据
Based on what?
物理学  长官
Physics, sir.
洛佩兹议员说
Congressman Lopez said
他跟卡洛琳·戴克说话的时候
that when he talked to Carolyn Decker,
他看见钱伯斯站在远处的墙边
he saw Chambers by the far wall.
鉴证组也的确在那里找到了他的指纹
Which is where CSU found his prints.
但几秒钟后  刺客就开枪了
But seconds later, our assassin opens fire --
连开三枪
three shots.
第一枪打在洛佩兹左面锁骨的下方
The first one strikes Lopez beneath the left clavicle.
第二枪擦过卡洛琳·戴克的肩膀
The second one grazes Carolyn Decker's shoulder,
第三枪打在她后背偏下的位置
and the third one strikes her in the upper back.
那一枪击中了她的肺动脉
That shot severs her pulmonary artery.
连抢救的机会都没有
She never has a chance.
这些怎么会让你们认为
How does any of this lead you to think
钱伯斯不是那个刺客呢
that Chambers is not the assassin.
钱伯斯的有利位置
Chambers' vantage point.
他是从侧面看洛佩兹和卡洛琳·戴克的
He had a side-angle view of Lopez and Carolyn Decker.
所以钱伯斯怎么可能从背后击中卡洛琳呢
So how did Chambers manage to shoot Carolyn in the back?
答案是他不可能做到
The answer is that he couldn't have,
除非那个子弹神奇的
not unless that bullet magically took
在空中向右转了个弯
a hard right turn in midair.
所以说开枪的人是从草丘那里开的枪
Which means the shots were fired from the grassy knoll,
-比喻说法  -贝克特探长
- metaphorically speaking. - Detective Beckett,
你真的认为他们的话可信吗
do you actually find any of this plausible?
是的  长官  可信到
Yes, sir, plausible enough that I'm getting ballistics
我让弹道分析人员回去重新做分析
to reevaluate the crime scene.
钱伯斯有动机
Chambers had motive,
他偷了张记者证  案发后他逃跑了
he stole a press pass, he fled the shooting.
-这些你怎么解释  -我想钱伯斯被陷害
- How do you explain all that? - I think Chambers
-做替罪羊  -可能是被卡尔·谢尔顿陷害的
- was set up to be the fall guy. - Probably by Carl Shelton.
那他为什么不坚称自己是清白的呢
Then why isn't he vigorously protesting his innocence?
钱伯斯不信任政府
Chambers distrusts authority.
而他认为我们也是陷害他的人
And he believes that we're part of a plot against him.
无论如何  艾里克·钱伯斯依然是第一嫌疑人
Nonetheless, Eric Chambers remains our prime suspect
除非有证据表明他无罪
unless proof comes in that he isn't.
在此期间  长官
In the meantime, sir,
我想再审问他一次
I'd like to take another run at him.
你是在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
我不会开口的
I'm not talking.
没关系
Well, that's okay.
你不用开口  你听着就行
You don't have to talk. You can just listen.
是的  我们知道...  你不是开枪的人
Yeah, we know that... you're not the shooter.
你当然知道
Of course you do.
是你们的人精心策划了整件事
You people orchestrated the whole thing.
我告诉你吧  艾里克
You know, Eric, I got a news flash for you.
你并不是某个大型政府阴谋组织的目标
You're not the focus of some big governmental conspiracy.
没人对你有一丁点的兴趣
No one has the... least bit of interest in you.
说实话  我收回那句话
Actually, I take that back.
有人对你很感兴趣
Someone is very interested in you --
那个陷害你的人
whoever set you up.
有人
Somebody went to
费尽心思陷害你
a significant amount of trouble to frame you,
而现在...
and now...
现在你知道的太多了
...now you know too much.
成了需要清理的目标
You're a loose end.
你可不会有什么好下场
I don't see a very bright future for you.
你真的指望我会相信你说的话吗
You honestly expect me to believe a word you say?
那取决于你  这是你的生活
Eh, that's up to you. It's your life.
只要告诉我你怎么进入后台的
Just tell me everything about how you got backstage,
我会保证你的安全
and I'll keep you safe.
如果不说  我就帮不了你了
If not, I can't help you.
没人能帮你
Nobody can.
你想想吧
Just think about it.
不过别想太久了
But don't think too long.
等等
Wait.
如果钱伯斯不是开枪的人
So, if Chambers isn't our shooter,
那他去后台干什么
then what was he doing backstage?
他想在洛佩兹电视演讲时与他对质
He wanted to make a political statement by confronting Lopez
表达自己的政治立场
during his speech in front of the cameras.
这样的话  他知道这会在
That way, he knew that it would blow up
24小时滚动新闻中播放
on the 24-hour news cycle.
那卡尔·谢尔顿怎么回事
All right, what about Carl Shelton?
卡塞尔  看起来这跟谢尔顿无关
Castle, it's looking like Shelton may not be involved.
这个亿万富翁实业家
The billionaire industrialist
手握权力的杠杆
with his grubby hands on the levers of power?
当然和他有关
Of course he's involved.
有人看到他们一起出现在储藏室
They were seen in the storage room.
那是因为谢尔顿
That's because Shelton
意识到钱伯斯想搞砸那次活动
realized that Chambers had crashed the event.
所以他想劝服他不要闹事
So, he tried to talk him out of making a scene.
钱伯斯到底从哪里弄到的记者证
So, where did Chambers get the press pass from?
放这他的信箱里
It was left for him in his mailbox.
他的信箱里吗
In his mailbox?
-谁放的  -一个匿名的支持者
- By whom? - An anonymous sympathizer
通过他的网站联系到他
contacted him through his website,
给他留下记者证还有
left him the pass, and instructions
如何去后台的指示图
about where to wait backstage.
好吧  我能说...
Okay, can I -- can I just say...
我知道我偶尔会
I know I have occasionally theorized
发表阴谋论
that a conspiracy was afoot.
只是偶尔吗
"Occasionally"?
不过这次  真的是有个阴谋
But this time, a conspiracy really is afoot.
伙计们  钱伯斯明显就是被
Guys, Chambers was clearly being manipulated
身份不明的人操控潜入后台
by person or persons unknown into being backstage
所以他可以成为完美的替罪羊
so he'd be the perfect patsy.
为什么有人会大费周章
Why would someone go to all that trouble
陷害他是射杀洛佩兹的枪手
to set him up as Lopez's shooter?
我也许可以解答这个问题
I may have an answer for that.
根据初级弹道学的报告  你说得对
Prelim ballistics report. You were right.
子弹不是从钱伯斯的位置发出的
The shots did not come from where Chambers was standing.
-那是从哪儿射出的  -根据轨迹
- So where did the shots come from? - Well, based on trajectories,
子弹是从这个位置发射出来的
the shots were fired from this position right here.
枪手站在照明支柱的后面
The shooter was behind the lighting stanchion.
这就是为什么没人看见他
That's why no one saw him.
开枪后他就从后面溜走了
He took a shot and then he slipped out the back.
那个地方的确很隐蔽
Yeah, it's good concealment.
不会有人看见他
Nobody would be able to spot him,
但从这个角度看
but check out this angle.
卡洛琳·戴克把洛佩兹挡住了
Carolyn Decker's blocking Lopez.
这就能解释为什么刺客没有射中洛佩兹
That would explain why the assassin missed Lopez.
除非他没有射偏
Unless he didn't miss him.
的确  卡洛琳·戴克几乎正对着枪手
Exactly, Carolyn Decker was almost square to the shooter
并且她也是被射击到中心位置
and she's the one who got hit center-mass.
各位  万一我们查错了方向怎么办
You guys, what if we're looking at this the wrong way?
卡洛琳·戴克才是真正的目标
And Carolyn Decker's the real target.
我们会彻查她的一切
All right, we'll dig through her life.
看是否什么人有杀人动机
See if anyone had motive to do this.
你们得先看一下这个
There's something you should see first.
这是来自艾里克·钱伯斯的住处
This is from Eric Chambers' building.
我在核查  把他的时间线连在一起时
I was reviewing it to paste together his timeline
看到了这个
when I saw this.
他径直走到钱伯斯的邮箱
He goes straight to Chambers' mailbox.
这肯定不是邮递员
Okay, that is definitely not the mailman.
他肯定是把记者证给钱伯斯
He must be leaving the press pass for Chambers.
这是什么时候
When was this?
枪击前三小时
Three hours before the shooting.
我们能看一下这个人的脸吗
Can we get a look at this dude's face?
不是很清楚
Not a good one.
天哪
Oh, my god.
怎么了
What is it?
是我的姐夫  弗兰克
That's my brother-in-law. That's Frank.
你确定那是弗兰克·凯利
Are you sure that's Frank Kelly?
毫无疑问
Yeah. No question.
莱恩  我知道这很难接受  但是
Ryan, I know this is hard, but...
枪击发生时弗兰克在哪
Where was Frank during those shots?
好的  我会在台上看着他
All right, I'll keep eyes on him onstage.
这就交给你了
You cover him back here?
他在帷幕的另一边
He was on the other side of the curtain.
他去了宴会厅来掩护洛佩兹
He went into the ballroom to cover Lopez.
你看到他在那了吗
Did you see him out there?
没有
No.
所以你也不是很清楚他在哪里
So, you don't really know where he was.
枪击后  他多久到的
After the shots, how soon did he arrive?
十秒钟  可能
10 seconds, maybe.
足够他从
Long enough for him to get
照明支柱到你可以看到他的地方
from the light stanchion to where you saw him.
所以  你是说
So, what are you saying here,
是弗兰克杀害了卡洛琳·戴克吗
that Frank killed Carolyn Decker?
他为什么要那样做
Why would he?
我不知道
I don't know,
但我们必须考虑这个可能性
but we need to consider the possibility.
至少  他参与其中
At the very least, he was involved,
所以我们要把他带来
so we're bringing him in.
很好  因为你知道吗
Good. Because you know what?
他会告诉我们他的说辞
He'll tell his side of the story.
肯定会对此有所解释的
There's an explanation for this.
肯定会有的  莱恩
I-I'm sure there is, Ryan.
没有什么会比这更让我们欣慰的
A-and nothing would make us happier.
伙计们  这是我的姐夫
Guys, this is my brother-in-law.
他肯定不会卷入到像这样的事里
There's no way he can be mixed up in something like this.
哥们
Hey, bro.
很遗憾
I'm sorry to say that
警员刚准备把弗兰克带过来
UNIs just tried to pick up Frank.
他一看到警车就跑了
As soon as he saw the patrol car, he bolted.
他们没追到他
They lost him.
发出全境通缉
Issue an A.P.B. see if there's any connection
看弗兰克·凯利和卡洛琳·戴克是否有关联
between Frank Kelly and Carolyn Decker.
我去查
I'm on it.
你要去哪里
Uh, where are you going?
我要去找到弗兰克
I'm gonna go find Frank.
我和你一起去
I'll go with you.
谢谢  哈维  但这是我的家人
Thanks, Javi, but... this is family here.
我想一个人去
I got to do this one alone.
好的
Okay.
我得和弗兰克谈谈  格温
I need to talk to Frank, Gwen.
他不在这
He's not here.
那他在哪
Where is he, then?
凯文  你难道一走进来
Kevin, don't you walk in here
就开始指责你自己的家人吗
and start pointing fingers at our own family.
他跑了  他为什么要那样做  格温
He ran! Why would he do that, Gwen?!
他做了什么
What's he into?
什么都没有
Nothing!
我知道这个表情
I know that look.
那是你以前
Yeah, that's the look that you used to get
偷偷抽烟
when you'd sneak a cigarette
跟妈妈撒谎的表情
and then you'd lie to mom about it.
格温我支持你  但我得知道真相
Look, Gwen, I'm here for you, but I need to know the truth.
他干了什么
What's he into?
去年家里的情况很紧张
Things were tight last year.
你知道  孩子们都在圣玛格丽特上学
You know, both kids are at St. Margaret's now,
费用很高
and that costs an arm and a leg.
可那之后家里慢慢有了一些钱
But then some money started coming in.
从哪来的钱
From where?
弗兰克说他在做些额外的工作
Frank said that he was picking up extra work, and...
但他并不是在公司挣的
But he never ran it through the company.
总是拿的现金
It was always cash.
有多少
How much cash?
加起来大概五万美金
Over time... close to 50 grand.
凯文  你是知道弗兰克的
Kevin! You know Frank.
你知道他是不会伤害别人的
You know he would never hurt a soul.
那就告诉我他在哪  不然他会受到伤害
Then tell me where he is before he's the one who gets hurt.
有莱恩的消息吗
Any word from Ryan?
没有  还没  这肯定很艰难
Uh, no. Not yet. It's got to be tough.
弗兰克对他来说就像亲兄弟一样
Frank is like a brother to him.
也许弗兰克不像我们想的那样陷得这么深
Well, maybe Frank isn't in this as deep as we think.
埃斯波西托还没有找到
Esposito still hasn't found
他和卡洛琳·戴克之间的任何关联
anything connecting him to Carolyn Decker.
我也没有
Yeah, well, neither have I.
最讨厌这差事
I hate this part.
检查受害者的个人物品吗
Going through a victim's effects?
是啊  尤其是手包
Yeah, especially a purse.
里面每一件东西都太私密
Everything in it is just so intimate.
让你有机会看到一个人的
It's like you get a chance to really see
真面目
who a person is...
或曾经的真面目
or was.
那卡洛琳·戴克的真面目如何
And who was Carolyn Decker?
她是...她是一个工作狂
Uh, she was, um... a workaholic.
手机上的日常闹钟设置为早上四点
The daily alarm on her phone is set for 4:00 a.m.
从她的日程表上看
And her calendar shows
她全身心地投入了净水计划
that she was completely dedicated to pure water now.
在她的钱包里有一封来自非洲小男孩
She has that handwritten letter from a little boy in Africa
亲笔写的感谢信
in her wallet thanking her.
他的村子由于霍乱几乎灭绝
His village was almost completely wiped out by cholera.
然后他们在村子里建起了净水系统
And then once they set up the water-filtration system
再也没人死了
in the village, nobody died.
她的确是有所作为
She was actually making a difference.
你也有所作为
You know, you make a difference, too.
但不如她
Yeah, not like her.
好吧
Okay.
怎么了
What?
她还有一部手机
She's got a second phone.
里面有什么吗
Anything on it?
对  谋杀动机
Yeah. Motive for murder.
你做了什么  弗兰克
What did you do, Frank?
跟你想的不一样
Not what you're thinking, man.
装得不错
That's a nice touch,
当我想起钱伯斯带着记者证时
the way you acted all surprised when I remembered
你装出一脸吃惊的样子
that Chambers was wearing a press pass.
其实你一点都不惊讶  弗兰克
Well, you weren't surprised Frank,
因为就是你把记者证给他的
because all along it was you that gave it to him.
你雇我干这趟活
You hired me for this job
是因为你知道我根本就不会怀疑你
because you knew that I would never suspect you.
你知道你能引导整个调查
You knew that you could steer the investigation.
不不  不是这样的
No. No, it wasn't like that.
没人会受到伤害的
And nobody was ever supposed to get hurt.
这他妈到底什么意思
What the hell does that even mean?
卡洛琳·戴克  她死了
Carolyn Decker, she's dead.
我深深自责  而一切都是你干的
I blamed myself. All along it was you.
凯文  我卷进了一些事
Kev, I got myself into something
我无法脱身
and I-I can't get myself out.
你怎么能这样
How... how could you do this?
你怎么能这样对待格温和孩子们
How -- how could you do this to Gwen and the kids?
看着我的眼睛告诉我
Look me in the eyes and tell me...
你有没有杀卡洛琳
did you kill Carolyn?
你认识她吗
Did you know her?
你杀她是为了钱吗
Did you do it for the money?
我没有杀人
I didn't kill nobody.
你一定做了什么  弗兰克
Well, you had to have done something, Frank.
你哪来的现金
Where did you get all that cash?
安保的工作
The security thing...
并不如我说的那样顺利
ain't going as good as I said.
生活不易  懂吗  我需要钱
Times are tough, you know? I needed money.
所以我靠卖通行证赚点外快
So I made some cash on the side by selling access.
什么样的通行证
What kind of access?
帮人溜进演唱会后台
Slipping people in backstage at a concert,
方便狗仔之类的
passes to fringe journalists,
就是那些无法从正门进入的人
you know, who can't get in the front door.
我向你发誓  我不知道记者证
I swear to you, I didn't know that press pass
会到钱伯斯的手里
was going to Chambers.
我只想为我的家庭  你的姐姐提供更好的生活
I'm just trying to provide for my family, for your sister.
我以为你会理解我
I thought, of all people, you'd understand that.
这记者证是谁花钱买的
Who paid you for that pass?
我已经把我知道的都说了
I've told you everything I know.
你就只能知道这么多  因为...
And that's all you're gonna get 'cause...
我们都很清楚警察进监狱会有什么下场
We both know what happens to cops in prison.
我不会去自首的
And I ain't turning myself in.
弗兰克
Frank.
Frank!
莱恩  抱歉
Ryan, I'm so sorry.
我姐姐还会更加难过
Well, it's gonna be a lot harder on my sister.
但至少不是弗兰克开的枪
But at least Frank isn't our shooter.
他知道是谁开的吗
Does he know who is?
不知道  他收到一个装有五千块钱的信封
No, he received $5,000 in an envelope
还有一个放记者证的地址
along with an address of where to leave to press pass.
钱是谁付的
And who paid him?
跟他联系的是一个叫曼哈顿政治的组织
He was contacted by an outfit called Manhattan Politics.
发现电邮是假的
Turns out it's a front with a dead e-mail address.
这组织背后的人陷害了艾里克·钱伯斯
So, whoever's behind this set up Eric Chambers
并利用了弗兰克
and used Frank to do it.
这笔钱我们能追踪吗
Can we trace the money?
还没查到  不过这钱是连号的
No luck so far. Though the bills are sequential.
有可能是从银行取出来的
So it probably came from a bank withdrawal.
那信封呢
What about the envelope?
鉴证组提取到了部分指纹
CSU pulled off a partial print,
但还不足以和数据库比对
but it's not enough to run against the database.
也许不用比对
Maybe we don't have to.
什么意思
What do you mean?
根据卡洛琳·戴克手机上的短信
Well, given the texts we found on Carolyn Decker's phone,
我们可能只需查一个名字
we may only have to check one name.
亚历克斯一会就能出院了
Alex will be discharged later today,
对于来自各地的支持
and we are so grateful and humbled
我们深表感激
by the outpouring of support from all over the world.
而同时我们也为
But it's also a time of mourning
卡洛琳·戴克的惨死深感悲痛
for the tragic death of Carolyn Decker.
我的丈夫将继续为这个国家的人民奋斗
My husband will honor her name by continuing to fight
继续为那些无法反映心声的人们努力
for the people of this country
以此来作为对她的纪念
and for those who voices aren't always heard.
谢谢
Thank you.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
贝克特探长  卡塞尔先生  你们怎么来了
Detective Beckett, Mr. Castle, what brings you here?
这个
This.
这里装着用来给艾里克·钱伯斯
It contained cash used to buy a press pass
买记者证的钱
for Eric Chambers.
记者证  杀手就是这么混进来的吗
A press pass? That's how the assassin got in?
你应该知道
Well, you should know.
信封上有你的指纹
You're fingerprint is on the envelope.
案发当时你在哪里  洛佩兹夫人
Where were you during the shooting Mrs. Lopez?
因为我们找不到你
Because we can't account for you.
你们难道认为我企图谋杀亲夫
You can't be suggesting that I tried to kill my husband.
不  不  当然不是
Oh, no. No, no, not at all.
我们认为你试图谋杀卡洛琳·戴克
We're suggesting you tried to kill Carolyn Decker
且成功了
and succeeded.
这指控既荒谬又卑鄙
That's ridiculous and despicable.
这是你丈夫与卡洛琳之间的短讯
These are texts between your husband and Carolyn.
有三年之久  那是奸情开始的时候
Going back three years, when their affair first started.
这是杀人动机  洛佩兹太太
That's motive for murder, Mrs. Lopez.
或许是纯粹的个人恩怨
Now, maybe it was purely personal,
或许是因为你把她看作是
or maybe you saw her as a liability
你丈夫成为总统的不利因素
to your husband's chances of becoming president.
无论如何  必须除掉卡洛琳·戴克
Either way, Carolyn Decker had to go.
但你得保证此事不会牵连到你身上
But you had to make sure that it didn't lead back to you.
于是你设局
So, you created a narrative
搞得好像洛佩兹先生被刺客刺杀
where Mr. Lopez was being targeted by an assassin,
让艾里克·钱伯斯做替罪羊
and Eric Chambers was the patsy.
这个计划既能提升你丈夫
A plan which happened to raise your husband's profile
在国内的关注度  如我们所见
on the national stage, as we just saw.
-好样的  -你们以为我不知道他俩的奸情吗
- Well done. - You don't think I knew about the affair?
我嫁给亚历克斯的时候  就知道会面对什么局面
I understood the deal I was making when I married Alex.
卡洛琳可不是不利因素
And far from a liability,
她是他的幕后顾问
Carolyn was his behind-the-scenes advisor.
通过她  他找到了很多支持他的
She was a conduit to major donors
-巨额捐献人  -枪击时你在哪  洛佩兹太太
- who backed him -- - Where were you during the shooting mrs. Lopez?
亚历克斯和我有个协议
Alex and I have an agreement.
我在宾馆
I was at the hotel.
717房间
Room 717.
如果真的有必要  我可以告诉你她的名字
I can give you her name if it's absolutely necessary.
有必要
It will be.
但这还是解释不了你的指纹
But it still doesn't explain away your fingerprint.
这信封来自亚历克斯的办公室
This envelope is from Alex's office.
我知道是因为办公用品都是我订购的
I know that because I ordered the stationary.
我有时在那帮忙
I help out there sometimes.
我给他的选民寄信
I send letters to his constituents.
我肯定是在那期间摸过这信封
I must have touched it at some point.
还有谁能拿到他的信封
Who else has access to his envelopes?
我不明白
I'm afraid I don't understand.
你认为我的人参与其中
So, you think that one of my people played a part in this?
那不可能  我亲自审核过所有员工
Well, that's impossible. I-I personally vetted everyone.
当我们知晓从何查探
Once we knew where to look,
我们找到了账单的匹配记录
we matched the serial numbers from those bills
出自你的银行账户提款
to a withdrawal from your bank account.
-我的  -准确地说  是你的竞选出行账户
- My bank? - Specifically, your campaign travel account.
那不可能
That can't be.
我是唯一有授权使用那账户的人
I'm the only one authorized to access the account --
只有我
Just me.
-和梅根  -她刚好
- and Megan. - Who is, oddly enough,
出现在银行安保录像中
who showed up on the bank security video
进行提款
making the withdrawal.
亚历克斯  这太荒谬了
Alex, this is a mistake.
我不会那么做  我没理由那么做
I would never do this. I have no reason to.
那可不是实话
That's not exactly true.
我们仔细查看了卡洛琳的短讯
We looked into Carolyn's texts again.
她对你有所担忧
She had misgivings about you.
卡洛琳认为在合适的团队支持下
Carolyn believed that you could make it
你有希望一路晋级  成为总统
all the way to the presidency with the right team in place,
但她认为梅根不属于那个团队
but she didn't think that Megan belonged on that team.
想到被排挤在外
The thought of being cast aside
令你无法忍受  于是你想出一招
was more than you could bear. So you came up with a plan
既能除掉威胁
that would eliminate your problem
又能让你的上司得到全国的同情
and win your boss the sympathy of a nation --
一石二鸟
Two birds with one stone.
我们拿到搜查令
We got a search warrant
搜查你的公寓  梅根
to look into your apartment, megan.
你穿的大衣上
The coat that you were wearing
检测出射击残留物
tested positive for gunshot residue.
你杀了卡洛琳
You killed Carolyn.
梅根  你怎么能这么做
Megan, how -- how could you do that?
我怎么能
How could I?
你怎么能那样
How could you?
你从市议会起家时
When you started at city council,
我为你在人家草坪上插宣传板
I was putting signs on people's lawns,
我在大冷天中为你分发传单
I was passing out pamphlets in the freezing cold.
我为你写演讲稿  我为你做账单
I write your speeches. I craft your bills.
我把全部都给了你
I have invested my entire life in you,
满足你的一切需求
In doing whatever it is you need me to do.
我做的很好
And I've done it well.
那些付出不应该被如此对待
That should count for something.
梅根·布鲁克斯  你因谋杀
Megan Brooks, you're under arrest
卡洛琳·戴克而被捕
for the murder of Carolyn Decker.
背后插刀  出轨  背叛
Backstabbing, adultery, and betrayal --
我就是因为这个讨厌政治
That is why I hate politics.
人民的代表应该是可敬的
Representatives of the people should be honorable.
值得信任的
They should be trustworthy.
有些是这样的
Well, I'm sure some of them are,
但华盛顿可能需要
But Washington could probably use
多一些像你这样思考的人
a few more people that think the way you do.
这是什么
What's this?
学习材料
Oh, study materials.
警监考试
For the Captain's exam.
-你要考吗  -这是我的下一步
- So you're gonna go for it? - Well, it's the next step.
还不确定这是该走的那条路
I'm not sure if it's the right one yet,
但想考考  看我能考成什么样
But I figured I'd take the test, see how I do.
如果考过了呢
And if you do well?
也许那会帮我做出决定
Then maybe that'll make my decision for me.
-准备好回家了吗  -是的
- You ready to go home? - Yeah.
我该怎么跟她说
What am I gonna tell her?
唯一能说的就是真相
The only thing you can -- the truth.
我搞砸了
I messed everything up.
即便是签了认罪协议  我还是要入狱
Even with a plea deal, I'm going to jail.
未必
No, you don't know that.
格温会恨我的
Gwen's gonna hate me...
我说了谎
For lying...
没能成为我应该成为的男子汉
And for not being the man I said I was.
她很坚强  比你想象的坚强
She's strong, frank. Stronger than you think.
我不知道是该敲门  还是直接开门
I don't know if I should knock or just open the door.
我错了  格温
I'm sorry, gwennie.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我们会撑过去的  宝贝
We'll get through it, baby.
会撑过去的
We'll figure it out.